Edward Bleier Papers
Edward Bleier Papers
1965-2007
Bleier, Edward
50.25 linear ft.
Ed Bleier worked in almost every aspect of radio and television communication, culminating in his position as president of Warner Bros. Domestic Pay-TV, Cable and Network Features division. Collection comprises both personal and professional files relating to strategy, management, analysis and marketing for Warner Bros. movie and television development and includes proposals, books, pamphlets, laser discs, videocassettes and DVDs, and multimedia materials.
2570332
Biographical History
Ed Bleier (1929- ) is an American radio and television executive. His career has paralleled the history of electronic media, with important roles in "new media" creation for Warner Bros., Warner Communications, and Time Warner. As of 2007 he was a board member of Blockbuster Inc., CKX Inc, and of RealNetworks, whose focus is streaming media over the Internet.
Bleier began his professional career with WNEW's "High School Hour" and The Long Island Press. He wrote for the Syracuse (New York) Herald Journal and for several Syracuse-area radio stations, and managed promotion for the DuMont Television Network and New York's Channel 5. In the early 1950s, while working at New York's Channel 7 and later at ABC, he instituted television-time sales to movie companies.
While studying at Syracuse University he worked as a copyboy for ABC News, and by the 1960s he was a senior executive there, having worked as Vice President for Daytime and Children's Programming and Sales; General Sales Management; and Marketing, Public Relations and Strategic Planning. Among his "firsts" at ABC were the first integration of African-American characters in daytime dramas and establishing ABC's first Saturday morning children's block, built around Warner Bros. Bugs Bunny/Looney Tunes cartoons. Over 40 years he oversaw some 100 variations of Looney Tunes programming on ten different cable and broadcast networks, propelling the characters into the top slots in both television and licensing/retail.
Bleier left ABC (succeeded there by Disney executive Michael Eisner) to become President of Warner Bros. Domestic Pay-TV, Cable and Network Features division, where he worked closely with Warner's cable systems to develop basic and pay-tv networks including MTV, Nickelodeon, TMC and others; co-created the corporate plan for home video; drove after-market sales of TV series and feature films to record-breaking levels; and pioneered new digital media markets such as content-on-demand and pay-per-view. From 2002 to 2005, Bleier served as Senior Adviser to the company.
In 2003 Bleier wrote the New York Times best-seller The Thanksgiving Ceremony, a work which grew out of his own first-generation American experiences (the book's foreword was written by well-known columnist and Syracuse University alumnus William Safire).
Bleier's pro bono work has included serving as steering committee chairman for 13 of the Aspen Institute's Communications Leaders Conferences, meetings which encourage dialogue between the communications industry's senior creative and business executives and their counterparts in government, economics and science. He was chairman of the Center for Communication, President of the International Radio and Television Society, Vice-Chairman of the International Television Council, Chairman of the Academy of the Arts of East Hampton's Guild Hall, and a former board member of the Keystone Center for Science and Environment and the Martha Graham Dance Company. He has participated in two United Nations World TV Forums and is a member of the Council on Foreign Relations and a trustee of the Charles Dana Foundation.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Edward Bleier Papers consist of 50 years of accumulated professional memorabilia and material covering the history of television (including books, industry, references, business plans, etc.) and animation (the classic Looney Tunes), various movies, posters, art books and pictures, architecture, audio tapes, etc. The collection is divided into nine series.
Animation files consist of professional working papers, documents and contracts about Warner Brothers animation characters: Bugs Bunny, Daffy Duck and Road Runner. This series includes correspondence with the animator Chuck Jones on various projects. There are also folders of deal work for all three television networks regarding cartoon programming. Of particular interest are a copy of the complete movie storyboards for Daffy Duck's Fantastic Island.
Cable files consist of internal documents and correspondence relating to the development of basic and pay-TV networks and pay-per-view digital media markets.
Licensing files comprise the bulk of the collection, and center on the licensing of Warner Brothers movies on network, cable and pay-per-view television channels. The documents with each movie vary but consist mainly of ratings analysis, negotiations, sales pitches, and general correspondence. Many films include notes from Bleier's office to movie directors on editing "objectionable" material, such as nudity or foul language, to allow for presentation on network television. Also included are documents regarding an appeal to the Motion Picture Association of America regarding the rating of the popular film, All the President's Men.
Media consist mainly of videotapes of lectures given by Bleier and his television appearance on Martha Stewart Living. There are also various Warner Brothers screeners and copies of speeches by Steven Spielberg and Stanley Kubrick.
Memorabilia contains miscellaneous commemorative industry "thank you" gifts, most commemorating conferences, anniversaries, and cable networks functions. There are also a few photographs and clippings.
Miscellaneous material contains an assortment of papers, clippings, brochures, and other miscellaneous material.
Printed material contains network TV program reports from 1987-1993 on cable television development and Warner Brothers TV movie distribution. This series also contains material and programs for awards and parties, such as the Guild Hall.
Project files contain a broad collection of working papers and projects throughout Bleier's career, including correspondence, deal work, contracts and working documents for individuals such as Chuck Jones, Friz Freleng, Greg Ford, Hal Geer, Jeff Bergman and Terry Lennon. Other projects include the creation of home video VCRs, the New York Cosmos Soccer Team revival, and facility information on Rockefeller Center/Radio City Music Hall.
Thanksgiving Ceremony files center on the preparation and publication of Bleier's book The Thanksgiving Ceremony published in 2003. There is extensive research on Thanksgiving recipes and research on the holiday as well as partial and full drafts of the book, e-mail correspondence and sales agreements. Events surrounding the book's publication are represented by book release party information, invitations and book reviews.
Arrangement of the Collection
Aside from licensing files, which have been alphabetized, material in each series remains in original order, roughly grouped according to topic.
Related Material
has a large number of manuscript collections relating to television, radio, film, and popular culture. Please refer to for a complete listing.
Separated Material
Published books in the collection have been transferred to Rare Books or to the general collections for cataloging. Please search for "Gift of Edward Bleier" for these items.
Subject and Genre Headings
Radio, television, film; Popular culture; Bleier, Edward; ABC News.; Time Warner Cable.; Warner Bros. Domestic Television Distribution (Firm); Looney tunes.; Cable television -- Marketing.; Cable television -- Planning.; Cable television -- United States -- History -- 20th century.; Executives -- United States.; Popular culture United States.; Subscription television.; Telecommunication.; Television broadcasting -- Archival resources.; Warner Bros. Cartoons -- History.; Books.; Correspondence.; Manuscripts for publication.; Photographs.; Proposals.; Pamphlets.; Reports.; Videotapes.; Businessmen.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Edward Bleier, 2007.
Inventory
- Animation files
  - BB "Compilation" Movie, 1991 (Box 1)
  - Chuck Jones Space Movie: "The Empire Strikes Duck" (Box 1)
  - "Made-Up" Movie (Box 1)
  - Tiny Tunes (Box 1)
  - The Acme Bros. Looney Tunes Show (Box 1)
  - The Bugs Bunny / Road Runner Movie, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - The Second Bugs Bunny / Road Runner Movie, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Bugs Bunny Movies: Kirschenbaum (Box 1)
  - The Mel Blanc Story (Box 1)
  - Bugs Bunny, 3rd Movie, 3 folders (Box 2)
  - Bugs and Daffy in Concert (Box 2)
  - Who Framed Roger Rabbit? (Box 2)
  - Bugs Bunny U.S. Stamp (Box 2)
  - WB Cartoons History, Wall Street Journal article (Box 2)
  - Bugs Bunny Birthday Special (Box 2)
  - Bugs Bunny's 50th Anniversary, 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Daffy Duck's Fantastic Island, includes complete movie storyboards; 3 folders (Box 3)
  - Daffy Duck Tapes (music for the movie) (Box 3)
  - Licensing Corp. of America, 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Tarzan (Box 4)
  - Animation, Disney Channel, thru 1989 (Box 4)
  - WHV Animation, 1990-1995 (Box 4)
  - Nickelodeon, 1990-1991; 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Road Runner (Box 4)
  - Bugs Bunny 50th Anniversary (Box 5)
  - Daffy Ducks 2nd movie, Quackbusters, 2 folders (Box 5)
  - Animation, General, 1992; 1993,; 1995; 3 folders (Box 5)
  - BB/LT All Star 50th Anniversary at MoMa thru 1986, 2 folders (Box 5)
  - BB/LT All Star 50th Anniversary at MoMa thru 1986 (Box 6)
  - WB Cartoons Golden Jubilee Museum of Modern Art (Box 6)
  - Syndication Figures (Box 6)
  - Animation, General, 1990; 2 folders (Box 6)
  - Office Space, Legal Documents, etc (Box 6)
  - Legal Documents, etc (Box 6)
  - Bugs Bunny's Hollywood Star (Box 6)
  - Atari/Animation, 1981-1983 (Box 6)
  - The Daffy-Speedy Hour Proposal (Box 6)
  - Bugs Bunny 50th Birthday Packet (Box 6)
- Cable files
  - ABC: Bugs and Tweety renewal (Box 7)
  - HBO X1 + X2, Etc (Box 7)
  - HBO Ratings (Box 7)
  - HBO, 1990-1994 (Box 7)
  - WB/HBO (Box 7)
  - HBO, 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Lorimar HBO Deal (Box 7)
  - Sky Channel (Box 7)
  - WB/Lorimar (Box 7)
  - Hits at Home (Box 7)
  - Pay-Per-View Boxing (Box 7)
  - Pay-Per-View Falcigno (Box 7)
  - Request Agreement (Box 7)
  - Viewer's Choice Packet (Box 7)
  - Home Video Sales Summary (Box 8)
  - MPAA TV Sales Report, 1985 (Box 8)
  - Business plan (Box 8)
  - WHTV station information (Box 8)
  - "New" file (Box 8)
  - Proposal (Box 8)
  - Radio deal (Box 8)
  - Gallagher Report (Box 8)
  - Wall Street Journal article (Box 8)
  - Stations (Box 8)
  - Radio stations (Box 8)
  - New York Times article (Box 8)
  - Project (Box 8)
  - Project (Box 9)
  - Notes, 11/76 to 7/77 (Box 9)
  - Ed's handwritten notes (Box 9)
  - HBO agreement and notes, 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Pay Per View (Box 9)
  - WB Shareholders Meeting (Box 9)
  - WB Communications Annual Report (Box 9)
  - Network Alliance (Box 10)
  - WCI (Box 10)
  - TWI/TWE (Box 10)
  - Cable Nets, 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Networks / Payscales (Box 10)
  - Profits and Sales (Box 10)
  - Cable Networks "Of the Future" (Box 10)
  - Pay-Per-View Initiatives (Box 10)
  - Lifetime (Network) (Box 11)
  - Network Material (Box 11)
  - The Wild West Marketing (Box 11)
  - Pay Per View Business (Box 11)
  - Channels (Box 11)
  - Basic Cable, 1/16/93 (Box 11)
  - Family Channel (Box 11)
  - Basic Cable (Box 11)
  - Time Warner Building Global Brand (Box 11)
  - Warner Brothers Pay-Per-View, 2 folders (Box 11)
  - AMC, 2 folders (Box 12)
  - Gems TV (Box 12)
  - CKX, Inc (Box 12)
  - Correspondence, Pay-Per-View (Box 12)
- Licensing files
  - "ABBA" (Box 13)
  - The Abdication (Box 13)
  - Above the Law, 2 folders (Box 13)
  - Absolute Power (Box 13)
  - The Accidental Tourist (Box 13)
  - Ace Ventura: Pet Detective (Box 13)
  - Ace Ventura: Pet Detective (animated) (Box 13)
  - Ace Ventura 2: When Nature Calls (Box 13)
  - Act of Piracy (Box 13)
  - A.D. (Anno Domini) (Box 13)
  - Adam's Woman (Box 13)
  - Addicted to Love (Box 13)
  - The Adventures of Brisco County, Jr. (Box 13)
  - African Portraits (Box 13)
  - After Hours (Box 13)
  - Agatha (Box 13)
  - Aida (Box 13)
  - Airborne (Box 13)
  - A.I. (Box 13)
  - Alice Doesn't Live Here Anymore (Box 13)
  - All Neat in Black Stockings (Box 13)
  - All American Boy (Box 13)
  - Alf (Box 14)
  - Alaska (Box 14)
  - All the President's Men, includes information on MPAA Ratings Appeal; 6 folders (Box 14)
  - Almost Heroes (Box 14)
  - Altered States (Box 14)
  - Amazing Captain Nemo (Box 14)
  - Amazing Grace (Box 14)
  - The Amazing Panda Adventure (Box 14)
  - America at the Olympics (Box 14)
  - American Dreamer (Box 14)
  - American Flyer (Box 14)
  - American Goes Bananas (Box 14)
  - The American President (Box 14)
  - Analyze This (Box 15)
  - Angelica: Voices, Visions (Box 15)
  - The Animal Within (Box 15)
  - Animals are Beautiful People (Box 15)
  - Animalympics (Box 15)
  - Anna Karenina (Box 15)
  - Any Given Sunday (Box 15)
  - Any Which Way You Can (Box 15)
  - Any Which Way You Can, versions of the Variety ad (Box 33)
  - The Apostles (Box 15)
  - Arch of Triumph (Box 15)
  - Aretha Franklin "Amazing Grace" (Box 15)
  - Arizona Dream (Box 15)
  - Around Midnight (Box 15)
  - Around the World in 80 Days (Box 15)
  - The Arrangement (Box 15)
  - The Arrival (Box 15)
  - The Art of War (Box 15)
  - Arthur 1 / Arthur on the Rocks (Box 15)
  - Ascent (Box 15)
  - Ashanti (Box 15)
  - "As Is" (Box 15)
  - Assassins (Box 15)
  - "Ask Julie" (Box 15)
  - At Play in the Fields of the Lord (Box 15)
  - Audio Visual Encyclopedia (Box 15)
  - Auntie Mame (Box 15)
  - The Avengers (Box 15)
  - The Awakening (Box 15)
  - The Awakening Land / WB-TV Development (Box 16)
  - Babylon 5 (Box 16)
  - Baby Maker (Box 16)
  - Back Roads (Box 16)
  - Bad Lands (Box 16)
  - Badmen (Box 16)
  - Bad Moon (Box 16)
  - Bait (Box 16)
  - Ballad of Cable Hogue (Box 16)
  - Bare Essence (Box 16)
  - Barefoot in Babylon (Box 16)
  - Barry Lyndon (Box 16)
  - Batman (Box 16)
  - Batman Forever (Box 16)
  - Batman Returns (Box 16)
  - Batman and Robin (Box 16)
  - Batman: Mask of the Phantasm (Box 16)
  - Battle Cry (Box 16)
  - Battlefield Earth (Box 16)
  - Battle of the Bulge (Box 16)
  - Bay City Story (Box 16)
  - Beast from 20,000 Fathoms (Box 16)
  - Beast Master (Box 16)
  - "Beatlemania" (Box 16)
  - Beetle Juice (Box 17)
  - Being Human (Box 17)
  - Belle and the Glory Boys (Box 17)
  - Best Friends (Box 17)
  - Best In Show (Box 17)
  - Better Off Dead (Box 17)
  - Beyond Obsession (Box 17)
  - Beyond Rangoon (Box 17)
  - Beyond Poseidon Adventure (Box 17)
  - Blood Simple (Box 17)
  - Beyond the Walls (Box 17)
  - The Big Bounce (Box 17)
  - The Big Brawl (Box 17)
  - Big Bully (Box 17)
  - Big City Blues (Box 17)
  - A Big Hand for the Little Lady (Box 17)
  - The Big House (Box 17)
  - The Big Land (Box 17)
  - The Big Tease (Box 17)
  - Big Wednesday (Box 17)
  - Bill and Ted's Excellent Adventure (Box 17)
  - Billy Jack (Box 17)
  - Bird (Box 17)
  - Black Beauty (Box 17)
  - Black Christmas; Silent Night Evil Night, Stranger in the House (Box 17)
  - Blade Runner (Box 17)
  - Blazing Saddles (Box 17)
  - Blue Rodeo (Box 17)
  - Blue Skies Again (Box 17)
  - Blume in Love (Box 17)
  - Bobby Deerfield (Box 17)
  - Bodyguard (Box 17)
  - The Bodyguard (Box 18)
  - Body Heat (Box 18)
  - Body Snatchers (Box 18)
  - Bogus (Box 18)
  - Boiling Point (Box 18)
  - Bonfire of the Vanities (Box 18)
  - Bonnie and Clyde (Box 18)
  - Born to Be Wild (Box 18)
  - Born to Ride (Box 18)
  - Born to the Wind (Box 18)
  - Boulevard Nights (Box 18)
  - Bourne Identity (Box 18)
  - Boys of the Side (Box 18)
  - The Boy Who Could Fly (Box 18)
  - Breaking Up (Box 18)
  - Bret Maverick (Box 18)
  - The Bridges of Madison County (Box 18)
  - Bronco Billy (Box 18)
  - The Bullies (Box 19)
  - Bullit (Box 19)
  - Burglar (Box 19)
  - The Butcher Boy (Box 19)
  - Bye Bye Braverman (Box 19)
  - By the Light of the Silvery Moon (Box 19)
  - Caddy Shack (Box 19)
  - Caddy Shack (Box 19)
  - Cahill, U.S. Marshall (Box 19)
  - Cal (Box 19)
  - Calamity Jane (Box 19)
  - Camelot (Box 19)
  - The Candidate (Box 19)
  - Cannonball Run 2 (Box 19)
  - Capricorn 1 (Box 19)
  - Captain Horatio Hornblower (Box 19)
  - Captain Nemo (Box 19)
  - Carpool (Box 19)
  - Carson City (Box 19)
  - Casablanca (Box 19)
  - Cats Don't Dance (Box 19)
  - Celebrate the Century (Box 19)
  - "Celebrate the Dream" Martin Luther King Jr. Special (Box 19)
  - A Celtic Celebration (Box 19)
  - Celebration Family (Box 19)
  - Chain of Fools (Box 19)
  - Chain Reaction (Box 19)
  - A Challenge for Robin Hood (Box 19)
  - Channel of the Apes (Box 19)
  - Charge at Feather River (Box 19)
  - Chariots of Fire (Box 19)
  - Charleston (Box 19)
  - Chasers (Box 19)
  - Charro (Box 19)
  - Cheyenne Autumn (Box 20)
  - Cheyenne (Box 20)
  - Cheyenne Social Club (Box 20)
  - Chico and the Man (Box 20)
  - Chico Mendes (Box 20)
  - Chill Factor (Box 20)
  - China Beach (Box 20)
  - Chips (Box 20)
  - Chisum (Box 20)
  - A Chorus Line (Box 20)
  - Christopher Columbus (Box 20)
  - Circus, Circus, Circus (Box 20)
  - City Heat (Box 20)
  - City of Angels (Box 20)
  - The Civil War (Box 20)
  - The Clan of the Cave Bear (Box 20)
  - Clara's Heart (Box 20)
  - Class Act (Box 20)
  - Class of '44 (Box 20)
  - Clean and Sober (Box 20)
  - Cleopatra Jones (Box 20)
  - The Client (Box 20)
  - Cliffhanger (Box 20)
  - Clockwork Orange, letters to and From Stanley Kubrick (Box 21)
  - Climb an Angry Mountain (Box 21)
  - Club Paradise (aka Island Jack) (Box 21)
  - Cobb (Box 21)
  - Cobra One and Two (Box 21)
  - Code R (Box 21)
  - The Colbys (Box 21)
  - The Color Purple, memos, broadcast standards (Box 21)
  - Come Fill the Cup (Box 21)
  - A Connecticut Yankee in King Arthur's Court (Box 21)
  - Coneheads (Box 21)
  - Conspiracy Theory (Box 21)
  - Contact (Box 21)
  - Cookie (Box 21)
  - Copy Cat (Box 21)
  - The Corn is Green (Box 21)
  - Country Matters, promotional materials (Box 21)
  - Court Martial of Custer (Box 21)
  - The Cowboy and the Cossack (Box 21)
  - The Cowboys (Box 22)
  - Cracked Up (Box 22)
  - Cracking Up (Box 22)
  - Crazy Times (Box 22)
  - Creepshow, T.A.P.E Consultancy Report (Box 22)
  - Crescendo (Box 22)
  - Crime Story (Box 22)
  - Crimewave (aka XYZ Murders) (Box 22)
  - Crimson Pirate (Box 22)
  - Crooked Man (Box 22)
  - Crooks and Coronets (Box 22)
  - Crossed Swords (Box 22)
  - Crossing Delancey (Box 22)
  - Crossings (Box 22)
  - The Crusade (Box 22)
  - The Crush (Box 22)
  - The Crying Game (Box 22)
  - A Cry in the Dark (Box 22)
  - Cry Rape (Box 22)
  - Cujo (Box 22)
  - Curly Sue (Box 22)
  - Daddy's Gone A Hunting (Box 22)
  - The Damned (Box 22)
  - Damn Yankees (Box 22)
  - Dallas, Photocopies of Promo Ads (Box 22)
  - The Dallas Connection (Box 22)
  - Dangerous Beauty (Box 22)
  - Dangerous Liaisons (Box 22)
  - Dangerously (Box 22)
  - Dark Justice (Box 23)
  - Dave (Box 23)
  - Day for Night (Box 23)
  - Day of Anger (National General) (Box 23)
  - Day One (Box 23)
  - The Days and Nights of Molly Dodd (Box 23)
  - Day of the Warrior (Box 23)
  - Dead Bang (Box 23)
  - Dead Calm (Box 23)
  - Dead Pool (Box 23)
  - Deadly Eyes (Box 23)
  - Deadly Trackers (Box 23)
  - The Deal of the Century, film license agreement (Box 23)
  - Dealing (Box 23)
  - Death in California (Box 23)
  - Death in Canaan (Box 23)
  - Death in Venice (Box 23)
  - Death of Her Innocence (Our Time) (Box 23)
  - Death Trap (Box 23)
  - Deep Blue Sea (Box 23)
  - Deep Six (Box 23)
  - Defence of the Realm (Box 23)
  - Defending Your Life (Box 23)
  - Deliverance, notes on making changes for TV version (Box 23)
  - Deliver Us From Evil (Box 23)
  - Demolition Man (Box 23)
  - Dennis the Menace (Box 23)
  - The Devils (Box 23)
  - Devil's Advocate (Box 23)
  - Diabolique (Box 23)
  - Dial M For Murder (Box 23)
  - Die Laughing (Box 23)
  - Dirty Harry (Box 24)
  - Disclosure (Box 24)
  - Disorderlies (Box 24)
  - A Distant Trumpet (Box 24)
  - Dive (Box 24)
  - Doc Hollywood (Box 24)
  - Doc Savage (Box 24)
  - Dog Day Afternoon (Box 24)
  - Dogfight (Box 24)
  - Don't Pave Main Street: Carmel's Heritage (Box 24)
  - Don't Tell Mom the Baby-Sitter's Dead (Box 24)
  - The Double Man (Box 24)
  - Dream West (Box 24)
  - Dress Gray (Box 24)
  - Driving Miss Daisy (Box 24)
  - The Drowning Pool (Box 24)
  - Drum Beat (Box 24)
  - Dukes of Hazzard, 2 folders; first folder includes ratings breakdown packet (Box 24)
  - Easter Bunny Is Coming (Box 24)
  - East of Eden (Box 24)
  - Eighty Steps to Johan (Box 24)
  - Eight Days a Week (Box 24)
  - Eight Is Enough (Box 24)
  - Eisenhower (Box 24)
  - El Cid (Box 24)
  - El Condor (Box 24)
  - Eleni (Box 24)
  - Ellis Island (Box 24)
  - NBC-Elvis (Box 24)
  - Emerald Forest (Box 24)
  - Emigrants/New Land (Box 25)
  - Empire of the Sun (Box 25)
  - Empire Records (Box 25)
  - Enemy Gold (Box 25)
  - Enemy of the People (Box 25)
  - The Enforcer (Box 25)
  - Ensign Pulver (Box 25)
  - Entertaining Angels (Box 25)
  - Enter the Dragon (Box 25)
  - Enter the Ninja (Box 25)
  - E.R (Box 25)
  - E.R, season two network rating packet and publicity (Box 25)
  - The Eraser (Box 25)
  - Escape Artist (Box 25)
  - Everybody's All-American (Box 25)
  - Every Which Way But Loose (Box 25)
  - Excalibur (Box 25)
  - Executive Action (Box 25)
  - Executive Decision (Box 26)
  - The Exorcist/Exorcist Two (Box 26)
  - The Exorcist (Box 26)
  - Extreme Measures (Box 26)
  - Eyes of a Stranger (Box 26)
  - Eyes Wide Shut (Box 26)
  - Fair Game (Box 26)
  - Falcon Crest (Box 26)
  - Fallen (Box 26)
  - Falling Down (Box 26)
  - Family Dog (Box 26)
  - Family Matters (Box 26)
  - Family Tree (Box 26)
  - Father's Day (Box 26)
  - Fandango (Box 26)
  - Fanny (Box 26)
  - Fathers and Sons (Box 26)
  - FBI (TV Series) (Box 26)
  - The FBI Story (Box 26)
  - Fearless (Box 26)
  - Fear No Evil (Box 26)
  - Feathertop (Box 26)
  - La Femme Nikita (Box 26)
  - Fennwick (Box 26)
  - Fiendish Plot of Dr. Fu Manchu (Box 26)
  - Fifty Days at Peking (Box 26)
  - The Final Analysis (Box 26)
  - Finders Keepers (Box 26)
  - Fire (Box 27)
  - Fire Down Below (Box 27)
  - Firefox (Box 27)
  - First Blood (Box 27)
  - First Christmas (Box 27)
  - First Deadly Sin (Box 27)
  - First Easter Bunny (Box 27)
  - First Family, T.A.P.E Consultancy Report (Box 27)
  - Five Days in Summer (Box 27)
  - Flame and the Arrow (Box 27)
  - The Flash (Box 27)
  - Flight of Dragons (Box 27)
  - Flood (Box 27)
  - Follow That Bird (Box 27)
  - For A Few Dollars More (Box 27)
  - Forever James Dean (Box 27)
  - Forever Young (Box 27)
  - The Forsyte Saga (Box 27)
  - Four For Texas (Box 27)
  - The Fox (Box 27)
  - Frankenstein Unbound (Box 27)
  - Frantic (Box 27)
  - Freddie's Nightmare (Box 27)
  - Freebie and the Bean (Box 27)
  - Freejack (Box 27)
  - Free Willy (Box 28)
  - Free Willy Two (Box 28)
  - Free Willy Three (Box 28)
  - Free Willy (Animated Series), Free Willy ratings presentation (Box 28)
  - Fresh Prince of Bel-Air, Fresh Prince and MTV presentation (Box 28)
  - Friendly Persuasion (Box 28)
  - Friendships, Secrets and Lies (Box 28)
  - Frisco Kid (Box 28)
  - Frost (Box 28)
  - Frosty's Winter Wonderland (Box 28)
  - F-Troop (Box 28)
  - The Fugitive (Box 28)
  - Full House (Box 28)
  - Full Metal Jacket, letters to and from Stanley Kubrick (Box 28)
  - Funny Farm (Box 28)
  - Gauntlet (Box 28)
  - Gay Purr-ee (Box 28)
  - Genesis Two (Box 28)